export const questionsA = [
  {
    prompt: "How many times do you shower in a day?",
    optionA: "Once a day",
    optionB: "Wash and dry",
    optionC: "twice a day",
    optionD: "Hmmm...on a need to basis",
    optionE: "I am into wash and dry",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Native dressing with socks and shoe or with Pam slippers?",
    optionA: "Why you go wear socks with Native?",
    optionB: "Pam slippers for me",
    optionC: "Half shoes things",
    optionD: "Defend on my mood",
    optionE: "Shoe with socks for me",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Team Drive or Team legedis?",
    optionA: "Team legedis",
    optionB: "I gat a fleet",
    optionC: "All these things don't matter in heaven",
    optionD: "Na bicycle i get, i no kill person.",
    optionE: "i no come this life to suffer.",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "To gym or Not to Gym?",
    optionA: "What is that?",
    optionB: "Who gym help?",
    optionC: "Spirit is willing but body is weak",
    optionD: "Gym all the way",
    optionE: "Eba no gree me gym",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Team 5 sec bathing or team I take my time to baff?",
    optionA: "I dey cook my skin?",
    optionB: "I take my time oh ( Celine Dion moment )",
    optionC: "E depend on if queue dey outside door",
    optionD: "Rush in Rush out",
    optionE: "It depends on my mood",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Team Tattoo or Team earring?",
    optionA: "Tattoo yes pls",
    optionB: "Earring abeg",
    optionC: "The 2 of them",
    optionD: "None",
    optionE: "The pain is madt",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Team beard gang or bear bear crew?",
    optionA: "Can't be bothered",
    optionB: 'Small "bear bear" crew',
    optionC: "Team clean shaven abeg",
    optionD: "Anyone goes abeg",
    optionE: "Beard gang all the way",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Tall dark and Handsome or Tall light and Handsome?",
    optionA: "Well Summarised",
    optionB: "Ofcos I represent all tall light and handsome dudes",
    optionC: "What about short people? Stop discrimination",
    optionD: "I am nobody's ex jor",
    optionE: "Omo na TDH I be oh AKA Charcoal coloured Iroko",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Change boxers daily or 1 week 1 boxer",
    optionA: "I sniff, e smell, I wash",
    optionB: "who boxers help?",
    optionC: "Team change daily",
    optionD: "Team weekly",
    optionE: "Twice per day",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Invited for dinner, who pays the bill?",
    optionA: "If no sugar mummy nko?",
    optionB: "Aunty aeg run am",
    optionC: "The guy na",
    optionD: "Person wey ask for bill ",
    optionE: "Who no forget wallet for house",
    answer: "D",
  },
];

export const questionsB = [
  {
    prompt: "How many times do your SPEC shower in a day?",
    optionA: "Once a day",
    optionB: "Wash and dry",
    optionC: "Twice a day",
    optionD: "Hmmm...on a need to basis",
    optionE: "He is into wash and dry",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Native dressing with socks and shoe or with Pam slippers?",
    optionA: "Why will he wear socks with Native?",
    optionB: "Pam slippers for him",
    optionC: "Half shoes things",
    optionD: "Depend on his mood",
    optionE: "Shoe with socks for him",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Team Drive or Team legedis?",
    optionA: "Team legedis",
    optionB: "He gat a fleet",
    optionC: "All these things don't matter in heaven",
    optionD: "Na bicycle him get, him no kill person.",
    optionE: "E no come this life to suffer.",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "To gym or Not to Gym?",
    optionA: "What is that?",
    optionB: "Who gym help?",
    optionC: "Spirit is willing but body is weak",
    optionD: "Gym all the way",
    optionE: "Eba no gree me gym",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Team 5 sec bathing or team take his time to baff?",
    optionA: "E dey cook him skin?",
    optionB: "he takes his time oh ( Boys to men for bathroom )",
    optionC: "E depend on if queue dey outside door",
    optionD: "Rush in Rush out",
    optionE: "It depends on His mood",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Team Tattoo or Team earring?",
    optionA: "Tattoo yes pls",
    optionB: "Earring abeg",
    optionC: "The 2 of them",
    optionD: "None",
    optionE: "He is afraid of the pain",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Team beard gang or bear bear crew?",
    optionA: "He can't be bothered",
    optionB: 'He is a member of small "bear bear" crew',
    optionC: "Team clean shaven abeg",
    optionD: "Anyone goes abeg",
    optionE: "Beard gang all the way",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Tall dark and Handsome or Tall light and Handsome?",
    optionA: "Well Summarised",
    optionB: "Ofcos he represent all tall light and handsome dudes",
    optionC: "What about short people? Stop discrimination",
    optionD: "He am nobody's ex jor",
    optionE: "He is aCharcoal coloured Iroko",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Change boxers daily or 1 week 1 boxer",
    optionA: "He sniff, e smell, he wash",
    optionB: "who boxers help?",
    optionC: "Team change daily",
    optionD: "Team weekly",
    optionE: "Twice per day",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "How does he chew food?",
    optionA: "You won't see his teeth",
    optionB: "You won't hear chomping sound",
    optionC: "He chomps away",
    optionD: "I don't notice",
    optionE: "That's why we don't eat outside",
    answer: "D",
  },
];
